myfirstblog.net 2011-06-02

# MyFirstBlog.net: free blogs, blogs for all

MyFirstBlog.net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: MyFirstBlog.net

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to gather demographic information, and for other purposes. Logged IP address is used to track users as and when necessary, e.g., when member has violated our Terms of Service or when required by law.

**1\. Cookies**  
The blog system uses cookies to save some info. MyFirstBlog.net also allows other companies that show advertisements on the blogs to access their cookies.

**2\. Advertisers**  
Our advertiser's ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies on the blogs, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers, and we do not have access to this information.

**3\. External Links**  
The blog may contain links to other sites. MyFirstBlog.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**4\. Blogs**  
This site makes bloging available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**5\. Children's Guidelines**  
This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.  
This site does not provide children notice of what information is collected.  
This site does not allow the parent to obtain the information collected from the child and provide a way for the parent to prevent the future use of that information.

**6\. Modifications to Our Policy**  
MyFirstBlog.net reserves the right to change our privacy policy which this website is offered. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement and our site, please please notify us by [Clicking here](http://support.myfirstblog.net/)
